Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee College of Health Sciences Records, 1960-2013
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1960-2013, UWM Archival Collection 49; 34 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 104 digital files (187 MB)
  - Proposal for Merger of School of Allied Health Professions and School of Social Work, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
  - Proposal to Implement BS Major in Allied Health, 1973, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 8-10)
  - Public Health
    - Planning, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 11-13)
    - Public Forum, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Rehabilitation Engineering Research Center on Ergonomic Solutions for Employment, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Research
    - Action Plan Summary, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - DIN, 1991-1996 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - NSF Grant, Technologies, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Program Priority Process, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
    - Research Growth Agenda Cluster Hires, 2007-2009 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Research Growth Initiative, 2006-2008 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Wisconsin Initiative for Biomedical and Health Technologies, 2004-2005
      - 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
      - Proposal, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Research and Graduate Program Committee, 1981-1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Retreat and Kickoff, 2005-2008 (Box 32, Folder 11-15)
  - Search and Screen Committee
    - Assistant Professor, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Assistant Professor, Epidemiology, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Assistant Professor, Medical Technology, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Assistant Professor, Physiologist, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Associate Professor, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Chemist Program, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Dean of the School of Allied Health Professions, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Director, Medical Technology Program, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Microbiologist Position, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Space
    - 1997-2006 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
    - Building Issues, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Clinical Laboratory Sciences, 1994-2003 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Columbia Hospital
      - Lease Agreement, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Site Evaluation, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Enderis, 1978-1995 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Klotsche Center, 1982-2006 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Klotsche Policy Board, 1998-2001 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Outreach, St. Michael's Discussion, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Pearse Remodeling, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Physical Environment Committee, 1998-2006 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Requirements, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Satellite Sites, 1998-2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Snack Station Project, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Task Force Final Report, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Temporary Relocation Plan, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Steering Committee
    - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Strategic Plan
    - 2000
    - 2000-2005 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Student Newsletter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Teaching Evaluation Summaries, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9-16)
  - TechStar, 2000-2002 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Program Review, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - UWM Initiative II Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - UWM Master Planning, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 5-7)
  - Urban Health Partnerships, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Personnel Files and Grants, 1977-1994, Accession 1998-048; 0.6 cubic ft. (2 boxes); Additions of personnel files, dating from 1980 to 1994, and grants, committee correspondence, Allied Health ads, curricular actions, and programs from 1977-1988.
  - Grant Files, 1977-1988 (Box 1)
  - Personnel Files, 1980-1994 (Box 2)
- Administrative Records and Personnel Files, 1963-2000, Accession 2001-014; 4 cubic ft. (4 boxes); Additions of administrative records including correspondence, auditing files, agendas, department and committee meeting minutes, and personnel files, dating from 1963-2000.
  - Subject Files, 1963-2000 (Box 1-2)
    Minutes for College-wide Faculty and Staff meetings, as well as departmental committee meeting minutes for the Health Sciences Department, the Department of Communication Sciences and Disorders, and the Department of Human Kinetics. Also included are program evaluations for the Human Kinetics graduate and undergraduate programs.
  - Personnel Files, 1963-2000 (Box 3-4)
    Both boxes contain Official Personnel Files. In addition, box 3 contains Executive Committee meeting minutes. These minutes pertain to personnel matters and are restricted.
- Personnel Files, 1978-2002, Accession 2002-075; 0.8 cubic ft. (2 boxes); Additions of personnel files, dating from 1978 to 2002.
- Personnel Files, 1992-1997, Accession 2003-047; 0.2 cubic ft. (1 box); Additions of personnel files, dating from 1992 to 1997.
- Personnel Files, 1963-2002, Accession 2007-016; 2 cubic ft. (2 boxes); Additions of personnel files, dating from 1963 to 2002.
- Personnel Files, 1972-2004, Accession 2010-003; 1.4 cubic ft. (2 boxes); Additions of personnel files, dating from 1972 to 2004.
- Personnel Files,1979-2013, Accession 2016-010; 3 cubic ft. (3 boxes); Additions of personnel files, dating from 1979 to 2013.